night this is me but ima scummy to J
that have been involved with a number saw for development projects over the
years
at a number of different companies have come to recognize scrum
as one of the best agile development practices in use today in this
fast-paced video
I want to show you why scrum is so great and how you can get started with from
under 10 minutes a cover all the course chrome concepts like product backlog
people's sprints burn on trucks and more
so get ready to be bombarded with information let's save this
is the product we want to build for this product we get all kinds a feature
requests from users
customers executives or even other team members it's well
the collection of all these features is called the product backlog another way
to think that the product backlog
is to think of it as a wish list all the things that would make this product
great
once we have our wish list or the product backlog
but it to start planning which specific features for point to put into it
particularly
release our product but we're getting ahead of ourselves
let's back up a bit built this product we need to have one or more people
party we're going to play a variety of roles first
we need her she plays the role a product Porter and helps make sure the right
features make it into the product backlog
representing the user's and customers are the product she hopes
set the direction of the product then we need this crap
he's the Scrum Master at his job is to make sure the project is progressing
smoothly
that every team member has the tools they need to get the job done
he set up meetings monitors the work being done that facilitates release
plant is essentially a project manager
but that such a boring title too will call him a ScrumMaster
implied he knows some jujitsu the rest to the team has similar roles to other
development processes
these guys build the product while these guys tested to make sure it works right
these games use it and hopefully pay for it at these guys generally get in the
way
but it turns out can't build many products without them but let's get back
to this
release planning the plan to release the team starts with this
the product backlog they identify the features they want to put into this
release
these features then comported the release back of the tape that
prioritizes the features
and has to miss them out of work involved for each feature providing a
rough idea
the full amount of work involved completed tire release
the quick side note about estimates their lot of techniques for creating
custom
from poker games debasing estimates on historical trends to using story points
is that about hours
but no matter what technique you use the want to make sure you involve at least
to or three subject matter experts there's simply no replacement for what a
subject matter expert brings to the table
keep that in mind as you do your estimates let's get back to this
the release backlog the prioritized leaseback login here
we're not ready to plan out several springs to get the work done
sprints for short durations milestones that allow teams to tackle a manageable
chunks for the project get a ship ready state spence generally range from a
couple days
as much as 30 days in length depending on the product release cycles
shorter the product's release cycles shorter each
Richard B and you want to have at least four as many as a dozen
strentz any given release so at this point we can take our release backlog
and split it up into several the spread battle
what are the most important things to remember about Sprint's is that the call
each sprint is to get a subsidy the product backlog worship ready state so
at the end the beach spread
you should have a fully tested product with all the features of that Sprint 100
percent complete
since Prince are a very short but a realistic representation apart
the product the late finished the spread is a great indicator that the project is
not
on schedule and something needs to be done therefore
it's extremely important to monitor the progress each sprint
with this a burnout the burndown chart is the number one reason
Force Ones popularity what are the best product visibility tools
ensure the project is progressing smoothly burn on chart provides the by
the measure
appear month work that remains in a given sprint release
in this crap you can see that the amount of work remaining bounces up and down
from day-to-day
is generally trending down towards zero because historical information is
provided in the burndown chart
its easy to see if the team is on the right track using the burndown chart
the team can quickly calculate this the slope of the graph
which is also called the burned-out velocity this is the average rate of
productivity for each day
for example a team greater productivity might be done on a typical day to finish
approximately 50 hours of work
knowing that it's possible to calculate an estimated completion date for the
Sprint or even for the entire release
based on the amount of work remain what's great about the burndown chart is
that we can compare our
actual velocity projected completion date what the team needs to do
in order to finish on time we can use that to see if it's a realistic time
frame
this is perhaps the most useful piece of knowledge that any team member product
owner
for product executive can have about the project because knowing whether or not
the project is on track
early in the schedule can help teams make the proper adjustments necessary to
get the project
on track burned-out truck provides empirical proof that the project is on
track
or if it's going to be late so let's talk a little about where the data for
this incredibly useful burned-out car comes from
as you recall are the least funny process was to create an estimate for
each feature
the product backlog the collection of these estimates forgiven sprint
represents the total amount of work that must be done to complete that Sprint
as each team member goes through and makes progress on one or more the
features
is simply update the amount of time remaining: for each with their own items
to the total amount of time remaining: a group of features that make up a sprint
changes on it day by day basis hopefully going downward until it hits 0
when the Sprint is complete breakdown chart aggregates that
remaining work data and shows it visually it's brilliant because it
communicates a massive amount of information
in just a few seconds at this point one question might have
is what we do about these little guys bugs come up during the development
every product while there's no way to avoid them altogether
there are some best practices on how to deal with them hearst
it's a good idea to track bike separately from features in their own
defect back lot doing a feature sprint any books that are found
relating to the future in development should be built with immediately
before marking the feature complete you also want to plan at least one or two
sprints the focus poorly
100 defect back that brings us to this
at the scrum from proponents after insisting
sure released an EP thank you behind a steady
is that if everyone is standing nobody will waste time and their poor
meeting will be short am i meeting daily you can feel confident that
everyone is on top of their tasks the daily scrum is a great idea
especially useful in less experienced teams but I wouldn't call it a
or essential part of scrap insisting on these meetings in an already efficient
an experienced team
especially teams that work in close proximity with one another
potentially backfire by laurin team or a keep that in mind when deciding on
having daily scrums
so there you have it scrum in under 10 minutes internal
all the essential concepts to start implementing scrum inside of your
organization
as quickly review in Squirrel you work with this
a product backlog which is nothing more than a list of features
he didn't break down the product backlog into one or more release backlogs
that for a given release you for the break up the release backlog
it to a number of Sprint backwards which are essentially short duration milestone
throughout your project event monitor the progress and each spread
using the burned-out depending on your team
you might want to have daily scrum meetings to ensure everything is on
track
that's all there is to it I hope you like this video as much as I enjoyed
making it
but before I let you go I have a quick assignment for you
open up your email client it send me an email letting me go what you thought of
this video on how it could be improved
feel free to ask any questions you might still have 0
and thanks for watching